<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>HSK Odyssey Fixes</name>
	<author>linyaDev</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>linya.hskodysseyfixes</packageId>
	<description>
[English]
Fixes Odyssey DLC compatibility issues in Hardcore SK modpack.

Bug: In TheGravship scenario, only 3 starting pawns spawn wearing vacsuits. The remaining pawns in the selection pool spawn naked because HSK's CopyPawnKindBasics() doesn't copy vacsuit-related fields.

Root cause: SK.GeneratePawn_DefaultXenotypeRace_Patch in Core_SK.dll randomizes PawnKindDef for extra pawns and calls CopyPawnKindBasics() to transfer apparel settings. However, it misses three critical fields:
- specificApparelRequirements (forces Vacsuit tag on Torso and FullHead)
- ignoreApparelAllowChance (bypasses generateAllowChance=0 on vacsuit)
- apparelAllowHeadgearChance (ensures helmet is generated)

This mod patches CopyPawnKindBasics via Harmony postfix to copy these missing fields.

[Russian]
Исправляет проблемы совместимости DLC Odyssey с модпаком Hardcore SK.

Баг: В сценарии "Гравикорабль" только 3 стартовые пешки спавнятся в скафандрах. Остальные пешки в пуле выбора появляются без одежды, потому что CopyPawnKindBasics() в Core_SK.dll не копирует поля, отвечающие за генерацию скафандров.

Причина: SK.GeneratePawn_DefaultXenotypeRace_Patch в Core_SK.dll рандомизирует PawnKindDef для дополнительных пешек и вызывает CopyPawnKindBasics() для переноса настроек одежды. Однако три критических поля не копируются:
- specificApparelRequirements (требует тег Vacsuit на Torso и FullHead)
- ignoreApparelAllowChance (обходит generateAllowChance=0 у скафандра)
- apparelAllowHeadgearChance (гарантирует генерацию шлема)

Этот мод патчит CopyPawnKindBasics через Harmony postfix для копирования недостающих полей.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Odyssey</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
